Previously on Reacher...
《烈探雷彻》前情提要
I got your message.
我收到你的消息了
110th, 10-30. A distress call.
110特别调查组 “10-30” 这是求救信号
Calvin Franz was murdered.
卡尔文弗朗茨被谋杀了
If he was calling you for help, he may have been trying to get in touch with the rest of the unit.
如果他给你打过电话 那他可能也给队里其他人打过
I called O'Donnell, Dixon, Sanchez and Orozco. No one's answering.
我给奥唐纳 迪克森 桑切斯 和奥罗斯科打了电话 都没人接
I paid off the concierge.
我买通了门房
He I.D.'d Neagley as checking in.
他指认内格利登记入住
Just keep an eye on that hotel and them.
盯紧那家酒店还有他们
No one will really know who you are. But you know.
- 没人会知道你是谁 - 但你知道
Hey, O'Donnell. Hey, Neagley.
- 嘿 奥唐纳 - 嘿 内格利
Just a list of names, all starting with the initials "A.M."
只是一个名单 所有名字的首字母都是AM
I just got page after page of random numbers.
我刚得到的是一页又一页的随机数据
No order, no meaning. Nothing. At least to us, for now.
- 没有顺序 没有意义 什么都没 - 至少我们觉得没有 而且暂时而已
What are you thinking?
你有什么想法
I'm thinking there's someone hell-bent on taking out the special investigators.
我觉得有人一心想干掉特别调查员
And they're coming after us.
他们是冲我们来的
Good.
很好
So, if someone's coming after the 110, how come they haven't made a run at the three of us yet?
如果他们的目标是110小组 那他们怎么还没杀我们
You were in the woods with your family, no one can ever find me
你之前跟家人在树林里 没人能找到我
and maybe they just hadn't gotten around to Neagley yet.
或许还没轮到内格利
They were in our hotel rooms,
他们去了我们的酒店房间
maybe to grab us or take us out, but then had to bail for some reason.
也许他们是想抓或者杀了我们 随后因故不得不匆忙离开
We need to try again to warn the others.
我们得再试着警告其他人
I'll call Sanchez and Orozco. I got Dixon.
- 我会给桑切斯和奥罗斯科打电话 - 我来联系迪克森
There's a black sedan across the street, couple houses down.
街对面几栋房子外有一辆黑色轿车
Same one as yesterday.
跟昨天遇到的是同一辆
Guess you were right. We're being followed.
我猜你说得对 我们被跟踪了
How you want to play this?
你打算怎么处理
I'm gonna go introduce myself.
我要去做个自我介绍
Look at this fucking beaut.
看看这个该死的美男子
What's he think he's gonna do?
他打算干什么呢
Fucking nose, man.
我他妈的鼻子 兄弟
Gun!
有枪
Just like the good old days.
就像过去美好的时光
Yeah, you on the sidelines while I do all the work.
是啊 你在一旁观望 而我把所有工作都做完了
Uh, fellas, this was his gun.
伙计们 这是他的枪
NYPD?
纽约市警察局
Name's Gaitano Russo.
名叫盖塔诺拉索
Don't look at me. You did all the work.
嘿 别看我 你把所有工作都做完了
Got to say, man. Major screwup.
我得说 兄弟 你闯大祸了
Soon as Russo wakes up, the entire NYPD's gonna be after your ass.
拉索一醒来 整个纽约市警察局都会追捕你
Why'd you got to hit him so hard, huh?
你为什么下手那么狠
I don't hit soft.
我出手从不手软
Well, a cop puncher's gonna do some serious time. I was pissed about the dog,
- 袭警可是要坐很久的牢 - 那只狗的事情让我很生气
and I assumed he was involved in killing Franzy and Swan.
我以为他参与了杀害弗朗茨和斯旺
What did you teach us? "In an investigation, assumptions kill."
你怎么教我们的  “在调查中 假设害死人”
No, it was "In an investigation, details matter".
是“在调查时 细节至关重要”
I didn't kill him, just broke his nose. He'll be fine when he wakes up.
我没杀他 只是打断了他的鼻子 他醒来时会没事的
Shit. Gaitano Russo.
糟了 盖塔诺拉索
Guy Russo. He's the investigating officer in Franz's homicide.
又叫盖伊拉索 他是弗朗茨谋杀案的调查人员
I saw it in the files. And how'd he get on your tail?
- 我在档案中看到过他的名字 - 他是怎么开始跟踪你的
NYPD saw the calls Franz made to you, flagged your name,
纽约市警察局看到弗朗茨 给你打了电话 标记了你的名字
got an alert when you bought the plane tickets,
你买票的时候 他们收到了提醒
been on you since you landed. Question is "why?"
自从你落地以后一直跟着你 问题是 为什么
Question is "where?"
问题是 哪里
As in, where do we hide a six-foot-five felon so you don't wind up in the pokey.
哪里可以藏一个近两米的重罪犯 这样你就不会被关进监狱了
I'm not leaving. The case is here.
我不走 这里是案发现场
Maybe not.
也许不是
When I called Sanchez and Orozco's office, voice mail was full.
我给桑切斯和奥罗斯科的办公室 打电话时 语音信箱已经满了
That's a bad sign.
这是个噩兆
So it might not be a bad time to get out of Dodge,
考虑到这位“拳王” 击倒了一位执法人员
considering Cocky Balboa here just knocked out a lawman.
现在出去避风头或许不失为好主意
Fine. We'll head down to Atlantic City,
好吧 我们去大西洋城
see if we can find the guys.
看我们能不能找到那些人
First we got to check out of our hotel and find a more generic ride
首先 我们要退房 并在拉索恢复知觉
before Russo regains consciousness and puts out a BOLO.
让警方“小心提防”你之前 找到更普通的交通工具
Range Rover's too conspicuous.
路虎揽胜太显眼了
You're the reason we can't have nice things.
就是因为你 我们才不能用好东西
Wait, I don't understand. Was it a car accident?
等等 我不明白 是出车祸了吗
No, he just kicked the car.
没有 他就踹了一下车
Well, then how the hell did the airbag go off?
好吧 那为什么 安全气囊都弹出来了
He kicked the car,
他踹了一下车
then he pulled the cop out and he knocked his dick in the dirt.
然后把警察拉了出来 狠狠地揍了一顿
I'm telling you, this guy's a beast.
这家伙就是头野兽
When the time comes, I'm gonna need some backup.
到时候 我需要支援
And you'll get it.
会给你安排支援的
But for now, you just stay on their asses, and don't fuck this up.
但现在 你继续跟踪监视他们 别搞砸了
Understood.
明白
Short-term airport parking only in Lot 1.
机场临时停车仅在一号停车场
There's a 2019 Accord for sale up in Tremont for way under market value.
特里蒙特有辆2019款雅阁 正在出售 价格低于市场价
Cash-only deal.
仅限现金交易
One of the most stolen makes and models for sale in the Bronx, and the guy wants no paperwork?
布朗克斯区最常被盗的车型之一 他不想要任何文件吗
We sit in that thing, we burn our asses.
我们坐进去 就跟火烧屁股一样
We don't have a choice. We're flagged in the system. We can't rent anything under our names.
我们别无选择 我们被警方标记了 什么都租不了
Well, we drive around in a stolen vehicle, we risk getting pinched.
我们开着偷来的车到处走 那很有可能被逮捕
I've got our solution.
我有解决办法了
How was your undercover job?
你的卧底工作怎么样了
Reacher.
雷彻
How'd you know I was undercover?
你怎么知道我在卧底
Considering the circumstances, you would've come right away.
考虑到当时的情况 你会马上过来
But you didn't, which can only mean you didn't get our messages until recently.
但你没有 这意味着 你最近才收到我们的消息
But if you were on vacation, you would've checked in with your office periodically.
如果你在休假 你会向你的办公室汇报
So you had to be working undercover, deep undercover,
所以你一定是去做卧底了 还藏得很深
where frequent check-ins aren't always possible.
没办法频繁签到
Same old Reacher.
你还是一如既往地厉害啊
Corporate embezzlement case.
我在调查一起企业贪污案
Stuck in Texas so long, I started to think
在德克萨斯州待了很久
I actually liked cowboy boots and high school football.
久到我都开始觉得自己 喜欢牛仔靴和高中橄榄球了
Still got your fake ID with you?
你还带着假身份证吗
- Yeah. - Good.
- 带着呢 - 很好
Use it to rent the car. What's with all the secrecy?
- 拿它去租车吧 - 为什么要保密
Neagley, O'Donnell and I have been flagged in the system.
内格利 奥唐纳和我被警方标记了
And I punched out a cop.
我还打晕了一名警察
Of course you did.
好吧 并不意外
So...
那么
Franz.
弗朗茨...
Yeah.
是的
And Swan, most likely.
斯旺也凶多吉少
Sanchez and Orozco are MIA, too.
桑切斯和奥罗斯科也失踪了
Okay.
好吧
Okay, so we take care of business.
好吧 那我们来调查吧
You do not mess with the special investigators.
不要惹特别调查员
Next.
接下来
Make sure you get an... SUV. I know. You need the headroom.
- 一定要租一辆... - SUV 我知道 你需要车内空间高点
Good. Glad to see you're still here.
太好了 很高兴看到你还在这里
Feel like I'm never gonna leave.
感觉我永远都不会离开
If it's reported at any Army base anywhere in the world,
如果世界上任何一个 军事基地报告了任何违规行为
no matter how minor the infraction, we're copied on it.
无论多么轻微 我们都得处理
Well, anything jump out at you?
你发现什么特别的事了吗
Yeah, a rat the size of a honeydew about 20 minutes ago.
是的 20分钟前 有一只蜜露大小的老鼠
- Seriously? - Yeah.
说真的
It's back in those boxes somewhere.
它又回到那堆箱子那边了
Gross.
好恶心
Well, speaking of rats, I think I smell one.
说到老鼠 我觉得 我发现了一只可疑的“老鼠”
A commanding officer at a base in Afghanistan thinks someone's stealing aviation fuel.
阿富汗的一名指挥官 认为有人在偷航空燃料
Siphoning off gas to resell it on the side?
把汽油抽走 然后再卖出去
Not exactly the kind of priority case the Army wants us taking on.
这不是军方想让我们优先处理的案子
Right, but see, I don't think anybody's stealing and reselling anything.
我觉得并不是有人在偷取并倒卖燃料
Take a look at these numbers. They always tell a story.
看看这些数字 它们总能说明问题
See, I noticed that every time fuel went missing from the base,
我注意到每次基地里有燃料丢失时
it was always after a specific flight.
都是在一趟特定的航班之后
Whenever C-17s ferried Humvees back home to the States.
即每当C-17 将悍马车运回美国的时候
I mean, it's a minor detail, but in an investigation, details matter.
我的意思是 这是个小细节 但在调查时 细节至关重要
I like that.
我喜欢这句
I'm gonna use it.
我会说这句的
What's mine is yours.
我的就是你的
So...
那么
you have a theory?
你推测出来了吗
Yeah. There's been no indication of black market fuel sales
是的 没有迹象表明基地附近
anywhere on or around the base,
存在黑市燃料销售的情况
so how does all that fuel go missing?
那这些燃料是怎么消失的呢
Best way to make gas disappear is to burn it up.
让燃料消失的最佳方式 就是把它烧了
Exactly. Now, Neagley's got the bulk fuel experience
没错 内格利有储藏运输石油的经验
and she thinks all the Humvee flights are intentionally being over-fueled.
她认为所有运送悍马的航班 都是故意过度加油的
But, when those planes land,
但当这些飞机降落时
the amount of fuel in the tanks is exactly what's expected,
油箱中的燃油量与预期相符
and that gets logged into the books.
这些都被记录到账簿中了
So, how does that happen?
怎么会这样
The excess fuel is being used to transport more weight
多余的燃料是在飞机运输不为人知的
than people realize is on the plane. Yeah.
- 额外货物的过程中消耗掉的 - 对
Something heavy and secret is being moved.
运输了一些沉重而秘密的东西
Exactly. Contraband in the Humvees.
没错 悍马车里有违禁品
Drugs, guns, stolen cash, all of the above.
毒品 枪支 被盗现金 上述所有
Good work, Dixon.
干得好 迪克森
You just found a case worthy of our attention.
你找到了一起值得我们关注的案子
I don't know about you, but all this sleuthing's made me thirsty.
我不知道你的感觉 但这些调查让我口干舌燥
Want to go celebrate?
想去庆祝一下吗
You can buy me a drink.
你可以请我喝一杯
I got to keep working on these reports.
我得继续处理这些报告
Maybe next time. Yeah.
- 下次吧 - 好的
But again,
但再说一次
excellent work, Dixon. Yeah.
- 干得好 迪克森 - 是啊
No problem. Like I said, numbers always tell the story.
没问题 如我所说 数字总能说明问题
So, the numbers telling you a story?
这些数字跟你说明问题了吗
Yeah, and it's a David Lynch film. It's totally incomprehensible.
是的 但这就像晦涩难懂的电影 完全无法理解
I mean, if these are supposed to be fractions, then it's sloppy work.
如果这些是分数 那写下这些数字的人就太粗心了
Some of them aren't even reduced.
有些没被约分
I noticed that, too.
我也注意到了这一点
Maybe the numbers represent hard quantities.
也许这些数据代表数量
Like, eight out of ten somethings, and not just four-fifths of something?
比如 十分之八的某物 而不是五分之四的某物
Maybe.
有可能
Yeah, maybe. Beyond that, two things stick out.
嗯 有可能 除此以外 还有两件事很突出
None of these are 100%, meaning there's no nine out of nine
这里面没有百分之百 也就是说没有九分之九
or ten out of ten, and the first four pages have 26 numbers,
或十分之十 前四页有26个数字
the fifth has 27 and the last two have 26 again.
第五页有27个 最后两页又是26个
Could be an accident. Just the way the information's spaced.
可能是巧合 只是信息的罗列方式
No, seems deliberate to me. None of these pages are full.
看起来是刻意而为之的 每一页都不满
What about the list of A.M. names?
那一连串AM开头的名字呢
Means nothing to me. I agree with you guys. It's got to be an alias.
没有任何意义 我同意你们的看法 应该是化名
Maybe it's someone with a grudge against the 110th?
也许是对110小组怀恨在心的人
We've arrested a lot of people.
我们逮捕了很多人
What about James Barr?
詹姆斯巴尔呢
I mean, that guy's got the skills and a screw loose.
他技术高明 有神经质
Barr's a shooter. Can't picture him throwing someone out of a helicopter.
巴尔是名射手 无法想象 他把人从直升机上扔下去的画面
Plus, I ran into him in Indiana last year.
我去年在印第安纳州遇见了他
He owes me now.
他现在欠我人情
I don't want to know.
我不想知道
Pine Barrens.
“松林荒原”
About a million lonely acres.
大约有一百万英亩
A lot like the spot Upstate New York where they found Franz.
很像他们在纽约北部 发现弗朗茨尸体的地方
They left his broken body out there to rot.
他们把他破碎的尸体扔在那里 任其腐烂
For all we know, Swan's out there, too.
据我们所知 斯旺也在那里
And Sanchez. And Orozco.
还有桑切斯和奥罗斯科
There's no blues station?
没有布鲁斯电台吗
Bro, we're in Jersey.
兄弟 我们现在在泽西
It's from my phone.
是我手机上的
Franz used to blast this at HQ all the time when you weren't around.
以前你不在的时候 弗朗茨总是在总部大声放这首歌
Leave it.
放着吧
They rented a car under a fake name, but it's, uh, it's Karla Dixon.
他们用假名字租了一辆车 但是是卡拉迪克森去租的
She's with them now.
她现在跟他们汇合了
They're headed towards Atlantic City, probably gonna try to find their missing buddies.
他们前往大西洋城 可能是去找他们的伙伴
Good. All in the same place at once.
很好 一个地方 一网打尽
When you get there, take them out.
你到大西洋城以后 杀了他们
Copy that.
收到
You remember what I said about needing backup? I know some local talent.
你还记得我说过我需要支援吗  我认识一些当地的人才
Well, bring in whoever you need.
你需要谁 尽管带上
We'll cover the tab.
我们会付钱
I just want them dead by tomorrow.
我只希望你明天干掉他们
You hear me? Fucking dead.
听见了吗 让他们死翘翘
Just like Franz's office.
就像弗朗茨的办公室一样
And our hotel rooms.
还像我们的酒店房间
You said they hadn't trashed Swan's place.
你说过他们洗劫了斯旺的住处
Yup. Add that to the list of things
- 是的 - 把那加入事物列表
that must mean something.
一定意味着什么
You guys ever know Orozco to go anywhere without his lighter?
你们知道奥罗斯科 会不带打火机出门吗
Better days.
美好时光
Am I the only one of us that doesn't have this photo?
只有我一个人没有这张照片吗
- Got mine. - Got mine.
- 我有 - 我有
On my bookshelf.
我的放在书架上
Hard to hang a picture on your wall when you don't have walls.
家里没有墙的话 很难把它挂墙上
We're wasting our time here.
我们在这里是浪费时间
Agreed. We have what the killers want, and anything worth finding,
我同意 我们有凶手想要的东西 所有值得找的东西
they already got.
他们已经得手了
Where to next?
接下来去哪儿
A bar.
去一家酒吧
Look at these photos of Sanchez and this woman.
看看桑切斯和这个女人的这些照片
Who under 50 frames photos? We do.
- 五十岁以下的人谁还会裱照片啊  - 我们会
Other than the 110th, how many photos you have at your house?
除了110小组那张 你还有多少照片
Not many. But she's framed, so she's important.
- 不多 - 但她的加了相框 所以她很重要
We're going to the Lucky Lounge.
我们要去幸运酒吧
No. You two stay here.
不 你们俩待在这里
You both look like cops.
你们俩看起来像警察
What do you two look like?
你们俩又像什么
Lady and the Tramp.
《小姐与流浪汉》
Hey. This woman working today?
嘿 这个女人今天上班吗
Who are you?
你是谁
Friends of Jorge Sanchez.
豪尔赫桑切斯的朋友
Hey, Dulls.
嘿 杜尔斯
These guys say they're friends of Sanchez, want to talk to Milena.
这俩说他们是桑切斯的朋友 想跟米莱娜谈谈
Take them back to the office. She's doing the books.
带他们去后面 她在记账
Milena.
米莱娜
Take your shit and get out of here, now.
拿着你的东西 立刻离开这里
I get that he's a different kind of guy,
我知道他不一样
but our commanding officer buys used underwear.
但我们的指挥官居然买二手内衣
Isn't that the girl from the photo? Oh, shit.
- 那不是照片里的女孩吗  - 妈的
Hey!
嘿
This is as far as we're going.
我们就只能走到这里了
What's going on, fellas?
怎么回事 伙计们
You guys are gonna stop coming around here and messing with our friends.
别再来搞我们的朋友了
Look, pal, you somehow got...
听我说 朋友 你有点...
Don't touch me!
别碰我
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
等等
Move your ass.
走啊
I'm done, I'm done.
别再打了 我受够了
Well, it's a good thing O'Donnell and I didn't go in.
还好奥唐纳和我没进去
Something could've gone wrong.
否则可能会出岔子
You making friends, big fella?
你在交朋友吗 大块头
I'm so sorry. I never would've run if I'd known who you were.
抱歉 如果我知道你们是谁 就不会逃跑了
I should've recognized you from Jorge's photos.
我应该认出你们的 我在豪尔赫的照片里看到过你们
My guys were just looking out for me.
我的朋友们只是想保护我
Scary dude came in here asking for her about a week ago.
大约一周前 一个可怕的家伙 来这里问过她
Said he was working with Sanchez and Orozco on some big security job.
那家伙说他和桑切斯以及奥罗斯科 一起在做某个大型安全工作
Broad-shouldered bald guy?
是个宽肩秃顶的家伙
No. He had hair.
不是 他有头发
Scar down his cheek.
脸颊上有伤疤
He wanted to know if Sanchez had left any kind of digital storage device with me.
他想知道桑切斯有没有 留给我任何数字存储设备
I-I had no idea what he was talking about.
我不知道他在说什么
I got a bad vibe off the guy, so soon as he left, I called Jorge.
那家伙给我一种不祥的感觉 他一走 我就给豪尔赫打了电话
He didn't answer.
他没接
They've gone dark before, part of the job, but this...
他们之前也因为工作失联过 但这次
feels different.
感觉不一样
Then you come in, claiming to know Sanchez,
你说你认识桑切斯
looking like the kind of people somebody'd hire to rough someone up.
而你看起来像是被雇来的打手
No offense. Assumed you were bad news.
无意冒犯 我以为你不可信
Do you know if Sanchez and Orozco had any recent contact
你知道桑切斯和奥罗斯科有没有跟
with Calvin Franz or Tony Swan?
卡尔文弗朗茨或托尼斯旺联系吗
Actually, yeah. He was here a couple weeks ago. They hadn't seen each other in forever.
他几周前来过 他们已经很久没见面了
I took a picture of them.
我给他们拍了张照
They were working a case together.
他们当时在调查一起案子
Sanchez told you that? Yeah.
- 桑切斯跟你说的  - 是的
What was it?
什么案子
He didn't mention details.
他没提细节
Was Swan involved?
斯旺也参与了吗
He didn't come down to A.C.,
他没来大西洋城
but I heard them mention his name.
但我听到他们提到了他的名字
You tried asking Franz about this?
你们问过弗朗茨这件事吗
- We can't. - Why not?
- 我们问不了 - 为什么
Someone threw him out of a helicopter.
有人把他从直升机上扔了下去
Oh, my God.
天啊
You think Jorge and Manuel are dead, too?
你们觉得豪尔赫 和曼努埃尔也死了吗
We don't know yet.
我们还不知道
If they're alive, we'll find them, but we need your help.
如果他们还活着 我们会找到他们 但我们需要你帮忙
Is there anything else you can recall that you haven't told us?
你还记得什么没告诉我们的事情吗
I don't know.
我不知道
Last time I saw Jorge, he was sitting on that stool right there.
我上次看见豪尔赫时 他坐在那边那张凳子上
He got a call. Seemed important.
他接了一个电话 似乎很重要
He say anything?
他说什么了
Kind of. He-he repeated a couple of numbers, kind of like he was surprised by them,
他重复了几个数字 好像因此很惊讶
or-or worried, maybe.
或者担心
Then he said he was going out for a while, and he never came back.
他说他要出去 然后就再也没回来
Do you remember the numbers? Yeah.
- 你记得那些数字吗  - 记得
He said,
他说
"650 at 100k each." No idea what he meant by that.
“六千五 每手十万” 不知道是什么意思
You're sure that's what he said? I'm positive.
- 你确定  - 非常确定
He said, "650 at 100k,"
他说:“六千五 每手十万”
he kissed me on the cheek and he ran out that door.
他吻了我的脸颊 跑出了那扇门
You remember the last words someone you love said to you.
你会记得你爱的人 对你说的最后一句话
We've got the numbers, we've got the New York plates.
我们已经掌握了数字 有纽约车牌
Maybe this isn't about someone with a grudge against the 110th.
也许这事与痛恨110小组的人无关
If you haven't noticed, it's pretty likely four of us have already been killed already.
我们中的四人很可能已经被杀害了
Milena said Franz was here a couple weeks ago.
米莱娜说弗朗茨几周前来过这里
If the guys were onto something that made them think we were all in danger,
如果某些事让他们觉得 我们处于危险之中
they would've called then, not weeks later.
那他们当时就会给我们打电话 而不是几周后才打
650 at 100k, we're talking 65 million bucks.
六千五 每手十万 我们说的是六千五百万美元
That's a lot of black chips.
黑筹码太多了
Most places. Not here.
大多数地方 不是这里
Atlantic City casinos rake in, what?
大西洋城的赌场大量敛财 怎么
Gross gaming revenue's got to be a couple billion a year, easy.
赌场的年总收入应该是几十亿
65 million, if taken carefully, over time,
六千五百万 如果随着时间的推移
could go unnoticed for a while.
可能会被忽视一段时间
Not that long. Not with casino accountants watching the take like hawks.
不会那么久 赌场会计会像老鹰一样盯着
But could the bad guys hide it in the margins long enough to get away with it
有没有可能是坏人将其藏得够久
before the calculator crew catches on?
在会计发现之前逃脱惩罚
Sanchez and Orozco do freelance casino security.
桑切斯和奥罗斯科 是自由职业赌场保安
I mean, maybe it all started with them.
也许事情是从他们开始的
They stumbled onto something big, they needed help...
他们偶然发现了一件大事 需要帮忙
So they reached out to Franz... maybe Swan.
所以他们联系了弗朗茨 或许还有斯旺
Guess this whole thing could be tied to gaming.
这件事可能与赌博有关
I'm Ellie, I'll be your server. What can I get you?
我是艾莉 为你们服务 你们需要什么
The casino's director of security.
我们找安全总监
Now, please.
请立刻带我们去吧
So, you're the 110th.
你们是110小组的
What's left of us.
是我们组剩下的成员
Sanchez and Orozco talk about you guys all the time.
桑切斯和奥罗斯科总是提起你们
Please.
请坐
So, you knew them well?
你之前很了解他们吗
Uh, yeah. They would do background checks for all the casinos on the boardwalk.
是的 他们会对木板人行道 所有赌场进行背景调查
Hold on. Uh, you just said "knew them."
等等 你刚说:“之前了解”
Past tense.
过去时
We have reason to believe they might be dead.
我们认为他们可能已经死了
Oh, shit.
见鬼
I-I just saw them, uh, while I was picking up lunch at White House Subs last month.
我上个月在白宫三明治店 吃午餐的时候还见过他们
How can I help? These numbers mean anything to you?
- 我能帮什么忙吗  - 这些数据有什么意义吗
Not offhand.
就这么看没什么意义
What about the phrase, "650 at 100k each"?
那“六千五 每手十万”呢
No. Uh, what's this all about?
不知道 这究竟是怎么回事
We think Sanchez and Orozco
桑切斯和奥罗斯科可能一直在调查
may have been looking into a $65 million gambling scam.
一起价值六千五百万的赌博骗局
Okay.
好吧
Uh, well, in that case, your "650" could be rigged slot machines or fixed hands of poker,
你们说的“六千五”可能是 被操纵的老虎机或固定手牌
but at 100k per hand, that'd be incredibly high stakes.
但每手十万 那可是相当高的赌注
And I can tell you right now, our books are on mark.
我现在就可以告诉你们 我们的账都是对的
All right? We're not missing a penny.
一分钱都不少
What about your competitors?
那你的竞争对手呢
You know, I can... I can ask around,
我可以打听一下
see if anyone knew what Sanchez and Orozco were working on.
看是否有人知道桑切斯 和奥罗斯科在调查什么案子
That might narrow it down for you. While you're at it, run these names,
- 那样可能会缩小范围 - 你打听时 也顺道查查这些名字
see if any of them are registered at a hotel in town.
看是否有人用其中的名字 登记入住酒店
Uh... you know, this-this might take a few hours. Where are you guys staying?
这可能要花几个小时 你们住哪儿
Don't know yet.
我们还不知道
Well, then, please, allow me.
那请让我来安排吧
Not necessary.
不需要
No, no. Any friends of Sanchez and Orozco.
那不行 你们可是 桑切斯和奥罗斯科的朋友
Well, it looks like all we have available is a suite.
看来我们现在只有一间套房了
I guess that'll have to do.
我猜那也够了吧
Come on, I'll get you guys settled in.
跟我来 我会安排你们安顿下来
We'll be fine at a motel. Reacher,
- 我们去住汽车旅馆就行了 - 雷彻
when someone offers to comp you a suite, just say yes.
当有人请你免费住套房时 直接答应就好
Yeah. We'll have them send you up a park bench to sleep on.
我们会让他们送你 一张公园长椅 让你睡觉
You'll feel right at home.
你会有宾至如归的感觉
What was that about a motel, Reacher?
雷彻 你不会还想住汽车旅馆吧
Whoa. I bet this place has a spa.
这地方肯定有水疗中心
I'm gonna take a schvitz.
我要蒸桑拿
Ooh. Dibs on the ocean view.
这还是个海景房
O'Donnell and Neagley found the bar.
奥唐纳和内格利找到了吧台
It's fully stocked.
里面“库存”充足
Not for long. You unpacked?
不过一会就不够了 放好行李了吗
Yup.
好了
I haven't been in a hotel that wasn't advertised as "family friendly" in years.
我很多年没住过 没标榜“家庭友好”的酒店了
I still can't believe David O'Donnell procreated.
我还是不敢相信 大卫奥唐纳有孩子了
On purpose, anyway.
还是计划生育
Yeah, I seem to remember someone bragging that the only people that would call you Daddy
我记得某人曾吹嘘说 唯一称你为“爸爸”的人
were the women you slept with.
是跟你睡过的女人
I still sleep with people who call me Daddy.
我现在还跟叫我“爸爸”的人一起睡
Sometimes all three of them if it's thundering outside.
如果外面打雷 我还是跟三个一起睡
You'll find out soon enough, Dixon.
你很快就会知道的 迪克森
You're pregnant? What?
- 你怀孕了  - 什么
No. Shit no.
没有
No, she's engaged. What, you didn't know?
她订婚了 怎么 你不知道
Someone finally lassoed our little filly.
终于有人套住了我们的小母马
No,
不
I, um, didn't...
我不知道
Yeah. Well, about that, you guys can, uh, unsave the date.
关于订婚那事 你们不必留时间过来了
Fuck. Seriously?
好家伙 真的
Yeah, I mean, you know me. I've always been a numbers gal, always had a life plan.
你了解我的 我一直是个数字女孩 一直都有人生计划
Plan said to get married at a certain age, certain year.
计划在一定的年龄 某一年结婚
And then one day, I see text messages on his phone.
然后 一天 我看到了他手机上的短信
It says, "Hey, sweetheart, can't wait to see you Friday.
说:“嘿 亲爱的 等不及周五见面了
I miss you." And all of that.
-“我爱你”等等 - 不是吧
No. No one steps out on Dixon.
没人能对迪克森不忠
Not even him, apparently.
显然他也不行
Text messages were from his niece who was visiting.
短信是他即将来拜访的侄女发的
But I realized that when I thought he was cheating,
但我发现当我以为他出轨时
I was, uh...
我...
I was relieved.
我松了一口气
I mean, he's a decent man. I...
他是个很正直的人 我...
I don't know, if you're gonna spend the rest of your life with somebody,
如果你要和某人共度一生
don't you want to feel something more than comfort?
难道你不想感受一些 舒服之外的东西吗
I mean, don't you want to feel excitement,
难道你不想觉得刺激
a little jolt of something when you see him?
当你看见他时 有一点震动的感觉吗
Anyways, you know, for a moment I thought I was gonna get out of it with no mess and no guilt,
有那么一刻 我以为 我会平静且毫无内疚地摆脱婚姻
but instead, I got out of it with...
但相反 我摆脱了婚姻...
A lot of mess and a whole lot of guilt.
却非常混乱 满满的负罪感
Bingo.
答对了
Good for you.
这对你来说是好事
Karla Dixon doesn't settle.
卡拉迪克森没有安定下来
Thank you.
谢谢
That's actually why I took the undercover job.
因此我接了卧底工作
Take a little time away from it all.
花一点时间远离这一切
Explain to me how undercover work and forensic accounting go together?
给我解释一下 你怎么会同时当卧底和法务会计的
Well, um, CEO embezzling millions from a company down in Texas,
首席执行官从德州一家公司 侵吞了数百万美元
where everybody's packing some kind of heat, and he was the kind of guy to use it if cornered,
那里每个人都携带枪支 如果被逼到绝路 他绝对会用武器
so got a little intrigue along with the number-crunching.
所以除了数字分析之外 还有一点吸引力
All right.
好吧
And what about you, Neagley?
你呢 内格利
Every time I check my LinkedIn, you're getting promoted again.
我每次查看领英网 都看到你升职了
I'm having fun.
我过得很好
On big cases, running a team now.
解决了大案子 现在带团队
Trying to land this huge software company as a client.
我之前试着 跟一家庞大的软件公司签合同
I pull it off, I get a taste of that fat contract.
我成功了 从那份值钱的合同里面收获颇丰
Making it rain.
赚了不少钱啊
No choice. I really want to get my dad on round-the-clock nursing care
我别无选择 我想给我爸请全天候护理
and rent him a nice place closer to me, but that takes capital.
给他租个离我近的房子 但那需要钱
Why rent? Buy and build equity.
为什么要租呢 直接买下来
Get a condo. Co-ops are fucking banana republics.
不 搞套公寓 合作社就是他妈的香蕉共和国
Yeah.
是啊
What about you, big dog? Being awfully quiet over there.
你呢 大狗狗 几乎音信全无
Home ownership is like keeping snakes as pets or ballroom dancing competitions.
置业就像养蛇当宠物 或参加交际舞比赛
Fine, if that's what you're into.
如果你对此感兴趣 那没问题
I just don't see the appeal. Or the appeal of a steady job.
- 但我不喜欢 - 那你觉得稳定的工作有吸引力吗
Corporate world doesn't seem that different from the Army,
企业界似乎跟军队也没什么区别
and that always felt a little like a cage.
总感觉像是个牢笼
Just didn't know anything else.
只是不知道其他的事情
Then one day I was in a bar, and someone plays Howlin' Wolf
我之前在酒吧里 有人演奏《狼嚎》
singing about trains going by in the night.
歌唱夜晚路过的火车
That sounded like real freedom to me.
那听起来像是真正的自由
Are you jumping on freight trains like Boxcar Willie?
你像博科思卡尔威利一样 跳上货运列车
Sometimes.
有时
Mostly I take buses or hitchhike.
大多数时候 我坐公交车或搭便车
What kind of lunatic is picking up the world's biggest drifter?
哪种疯子才会让世界上 块头最大的流浪汉上车啊
They can be interesting. Where do you eat?
- 他们很有意思 - 你在哪里吃饭
I steal pie off windowsills.
我从窗台上偷馅饼
I'm being serious. Diners.
- 我说真的 - 小饭馆
Sometimes people who pick me up share a meal with me.
有时让我搭便车的人 会分享食物 跟我一起吃饭
Sometimes I share with them. Where do you sleep?
- 有时是我分享给他们 - 你睡哪儿
Cheap motels mostly.
大多数时候住在廉价汽车旅馆里
And what if you can't find one?
如果你找不到汽车旅馆呢
Unattended boats in marinas are good for a night.
停泊在码头的无人看管的船只 也很适合住一晚
Flatbeds of parked trucks.
熄火的卡车的平板也适合
Had a great night's sleep in a hammock I spotted in some guy's backyard once
有一次 我在发现的吊床上 睡了个好觉
till the sprinklers went off. Good God, man.
- 可惜洒水器浇灭了我的美梦 - 天啊
All you need is a stick and a bindle. Too much luggage.
- 你还真是一根棍和一块布就走天下 - 行李太多了
Any more questions?
还有问题吗
Yeah, just one.
有 只有一个
Don't you ever get lonely?
你从来不觉得孤单吗
Looks like someone took the sign as a personal challenge.
有人把标语当成个人挑战了呀
Doreen, I'm just warming up.
多琳 我只是在热身
If you liked the dinner, make sure to try Neptune's breakfast buffet.
如果你喜欢晚餐 请务必试一下尼普顿的自助早餐
Every day, starting at 6:00 a.m.
每天早上六点开始
Thank you.
谢谢
Looks like I'm not the only one who couldn't sleep.
看来我不是唯一一个睡不着的
Numbers relax me.
数字让我放松
Figured if I was gonna do math, I might as well make some walking-around money. Stand.
如果我要做点数学计算 不如顺便赚点钱 我要叫停
Ma'am, you're showing ten and eight on two of your hands.
你的两只手上显示的是十和八
That's right. And I could double down and risk it all for a potentially larger payout.
没错 我可以加倍下注 赌上一切换取更大的回报
Or I could stand and have a guaranteed win
或者我也可以叫停 保证能获胜
because the next card out of that shoe is gonna bust you.
因为下一张牌亮牌时 你就输光了
My grandmother always said, pigs get fat, hogs get slaughtered.
我祖母曾经说 “不可人心不足蛇吞象”
She's no hog.
她可不是蛇
I'm no hog, so I'm gonna stand.
我不是蛇 所以我要叫停
As you wish.
如你所愿
15...
十五
Too many.
太多了
Congratulations, ma'am.
恭喜你 女士
You're having a very lucky night.
你今晚非常幸运
Maybe you'd like to celebrate with a concert on us?
我们想请你去听音乐会 庆祝一下
Thank you. Ladies of the '80s.
- 谢谢 - 八十年代的女士们
Debbie Gibson, Tiffany, and Taylor Dane performing their biggest hits.
黛比吉布森 蒂芙尼和泰勒戴恩 会表演她们最热门的歌曲
If you hurry, you can actually catch the second half.
你可以赶上下半场
But I'm having fun.
但我玩得很开心
Ma'am, we know you're counting cards.
我们知道你在算牌
Which isn't illegal if you do it in your head.
用脑子算牌是合法的
But seeing that your chief of security was kind enough to comp us a suite,
但鉴于你们的安全主管 好心给我们安排了一间套房
I'll cut you some slack.
我就放你们一马吧
Want to use those muscles and help me carry these to the cashier window?
动动你的肌肉 把这些筹码送到收银窗口去
And you can give these tickets to the guy in the Members Only jacket.
把这些票给穿着会员专用夹克的人
He looks like he would enjoy some '80s ladies.
他看起来很喜欢八十年代的女士
Thanks for coming with.
谢谢你陪我
Late-night walks always clear my head,
深夜散步总能让我头脑清醒
and after the text I got from Neagley about Franz, my head's been kind of cloudy, you know?
我收到内格利发来说弗朗茨死了的 短信后 我的脑子就一直有点乱
Yeah.
是啊
I'm surprised you can walk at all with all the casino's money in your pockets.
我很惊讶你口袋里 装着赌场赚来的那些钱还能散步
Can I assume the forensic accountant's gonna declare that cash on her taxes?
我猜法务会计会在税款申报的时候 附上这一笔钱吧
Those crooks?
那些骗子
If there's anybody I could audit... Actually, it's kind of my dream job.
要是我能审计某人的话 那简直是我梦想的工作
Current gig doesn't give you your auditing fix?
现在的工作满足不了你吗
No, I'm just busting millionaires from stealing from billionaires.
不行 我正在抓一个 从亿万富翁那里偷钱的百万富翁
What I really want to do is go after government corruption and waste.
我想做的是追查 政府的腐败和浪费行为
Oh, you used to work for Uncle Sam.
你以前在山姆大叔手下工作过
You know what I'm talking about. $600 toilet seats. Exactly.
- 六百美元的坐便圈 - 没错
I mean, if tax money was spent efficiently, honestly, we could fix roads and bridges
如果税收能被有效使用 我们可以修路和桥梁
and schools. Like, we could help people who actually need help.
以及学校 我们可以帮助需要帮助的人
We could make a difference.
我们可以有所作为
You should do it.
你应该这么做
Yeah.
是啊
Well, I looked into starting my own nonprofit watchdog group,
我考虑过自己成立非营利监督组织
but start-up costs are prohibitive.
但启动成本让人望而却步
First step's always the hardest.
第一步总是最难的
Yeah.
是的
Is that why, back in the day, you and I never happened?
这就是我们以前 从没有发生过关系的原因吗
First steps were the hardest?
第一步是最难的
How much did you drink back at the hotel room?
你在酒店房间里喝了多少
Enough to ask you that question.
足够我问你那个问题了
I mean, come on, Reacher. It's not like I didn't drop any hints.
快说 我以前给过你提示
I was your boss.
当时我是你的老大
It wouldn't have been right.
那样做不对
Wow. [sighs] Well, I waited years for that answer, and it's pure Reacher.
我等了好几年才等到这个答案 不愧是你雷彻的作风
Direct, honest and well-reasoned.
直接 诚实且有理有据
So, can I ask you another question?
我能再问你个问题吗
What do you want to do about the two guys that are following us?
你想怎么对付那两个跟踪我们的人
When'd you spot them? Ooh, when we left the casino.
- 你什么时候发现的  - 我们离开赌场时就发现了
Figure they saw us cashing out and now they're gonna try to rob us.
我以为他们是看到我们兑的现金 想抢劫我们
That's what I thought, too.
我本来也是这么想的
But see that car
看见停在那边
parked up the street with the New York dealer tags? Yeah.
- 有纽约临时牌照的车了吗  - 怎么了
Pretty sure it was behind us on the expressway when we came into town.
我们进城时 它在高速路上跟着我们
Also, pretty sure when we walk by it, a man with a gun will step out.
我们经过它时 肯定会有个持枪的男人走出来
Then, when we turn to run, the guys behind us won't be so far behind anymore.
我们转身逃跑时 我们身后的人 不会离得那么远
So what's the plan?
计划是什么
We're not gonna walk by that car.
我们不会经过那辆车
On my "go," over the fence.
我说“走” 就翻过栅栏
Go.
走
Fuck.
他妈的
Okay, there's got to be a warrant out for you in New York for hitting that cop.
好的 因为你打了那个警察 肯定会发布你的逮捕令
We open fire in a residential area, cops get called, you get locked up.
如果我们在住宅区开枪 警察就会被叫来 你会被关起来
Let's do this without guns.
我们别用枪
Looks like they have the same idea.
看起来他们也是这么想的
Need help with yours?
需要我帮你处理你负责的人吗
I'll manage.
我能处理
Damn, Reacher. When we were kids, we just wrote our names in it.
该死 我们小时候 会把名字写在混凝土里
It's the Members Only jacket guy from the casino.
是赌场里穿着会员专用夹克的男人
Oh, shit. If they went after us, they might go after Neagley and O'Donnell, too.
妈的 如果他们追杀我们 他们可能也会去追杀内格利和奥唐纳
No, they waited until we were off the boardwalk to make their move.
不会 他们一直等到我们离开 木板人行道才动手
They're not gonna go into a busy hotel with cameras everywhere.
他们不会去 到处都是监控的繁忙的酒店
No I.D.
没有身份证
Let's search this asshole's car.
我们搜一下这个混蛋的车
Looks like someone did their homework.
看起来有人做了功课
Phone.
手机
Is it done?
成了吗
Not in the way you expected.
成是成了 就是跟你想的不一样
You're fucking with the wrong guy, Reacher.
你惹错人了
You should know that this doesn't end well for you.
你应该知道你不会有好下场的
Then why are you the one that sounds scared?
那为什么是你听起来在瑟瑟发抖
Think I got his attention. Should we trace the number?
- 我觉得我引起他的注意了 - 我们要追踪号码吗
This is a burner. Guy on the other end will be using a burner, too.
这是一次性手机 刚才接电话那人也会用一次性手机
Dealer tags are most likely ghost plates, VIN's been scratched off.
临时牌照是幽灵车牌 车牌号已经被刮掉了
Nothing to I.D. any of them.
没什么能指认他们身份的东西
These guys are pros.
这些人都是专业杀手
We should've left one of them alive.
我们应该留个活口的
Yeah, but they didn't give us much of a choice, did they?
是啊 他们没给我们很多选择
Maybe not. Now we have nothing to go on.
也许没有 现在我们的线索断了
Not necessarily.
不一定
Parking lot pass.
停车场通行证
"New Age Technologies." Yeah.
-“新时代科技” - 对
Stamped yesterday morning.
昨天早上盖的章
I think it's what you call a clue.
这就是你口中的线索
Now what are we gonna do about those bodies?
我们怎么处理尸体
I have an idea.
我有个主意
I'm thirsty.
我口渴了
Want to get a beer?
想喝啤酒吗
Anything on New Age?
新时代有什么发现吗
Yeah,
有
looks like New Age is an aerospace company.
看起来新时代是一家航空航天公司
Any ties to Atlantic City?
跟大西洋城有联系吗
Not that I can see. Headquarters are based in New York.
我看没有 它的总部设在纽约
Looks like a piece of shrapnel bit me. I didn't notice with all the adrenaline pumping.
有一块弹片打中我了 刚才太过刺激 我没注意
Barely winged you.
几乎没伤到你
Here.
这里...
What you doing?
你在干什么
What my mom used to do when the alcohol stung.
给伤口抹酒精很疼 我妈以前就这么做
You know, you're probably just blowing germs into it.
你可能只把细菌吹进去了
Probably. But it feels good.
可能吧 但感觉很好
Thanks.
谢谢
Welcome.
不用谢
You know, Reacher,
你知道 雷彻
it's perfectly normal to be lonely sometimes.
有时感觉孤单是很正常的
Anyone living their life the way you do would.
任何人像你这么过日子都会孤单
But you don't have to be lonely tonight.
今晚你不必孤单
And you're not my boss anymore.
而且你也不再是我的老大了
All 650 will be in the truck.
所有六千五百万都将装在卡车里
You can track the shipment with the GPS locater I paired to this.
你可以用我在车上 装的GPS定位器追踪
There are at least two good ambush points marked on the route.
路上至少标记了两个好的伏击点
Excellent.
很好
My men will take care of the rest.
我的人会处理剩下的事
And the weapons?
那武器呢
They'll all be used overseas? I was told that was the deal.
都会在海外使用吗 这是说好了的
Absolutely.
那当然
And the, and the truck driver won't be harmed?
卡车司机不会受到伤害吧
Of course.
当然
I would never harm anyone.
我永远不会伤害任何人
Morning, Dixon. We need to talk to you about what happened last night.
- 早上好 迪克森 - 我们需要谈谈昨晚的事
Oh, the whole hotel heard what happened last night.
整个酒店都听到昨天的动静了
Told you you were loud.
我就说你声音很大
Found this in a car that followed us down from New York yesterday.
这是昨天在从纽约就开始 跟踪我们的车里找到的
What happened to the driver?
司机怎么了
He won't be following us back.
他不会跟我们回去
Neither will his two friends.
他的那两个朋友也不会
Shit.
妈的
Who is it? Wright.
- 是谁  - 赖特
Clear.
安全
Come on in.
进来
You, uh, you folks seem a little jumpy.
你们看起来有点紧张啊
I mean, I don't blame you, given the circumstances.
鉴于目前的情况 我不能怪你们
And I hate to be the bearer of more bad news, but when I was looking into things,
我很讨厌传达更多坏消息 但我调查这些事情时
Atlantic City PD told me that two more bodies have been discovered in Upstate New York,
大西洋城警察局跟我说 他们在纽约北部发现了两具尸体
near where they found your other friend.
就在他们发现你们朋友的地方附近
Judging by the decomposition, they'd been there a while.
从分解情况来看 他们已经在那儿有段时间了
Got a copy of the police report for you.
我拿到了一份警察报告副本
Pretty easy to I.D. him with that.
很容易借此识别其身份
When he joined the Army, his sister was terrified
他参军时 他姐姐很害怕
he'd be killed with some disfiguring wounds.
他会伤痕累累地死去
She'd never know what happened to him.
她永远不会知道发生了什么
Said his dog tags could be blown off.
就说他的兵牌可能被炸掉
To calm her down, he got his name and service number tattooed across his back.
为了安抚她 他在后背上 文了他的名字和服役编号
Looked ridiculous.
看起来很可笑
He didn't care.
他不在乎
He loved his sister.
他爱他的姐姐
I'm gonna have to call her.
我得给她打电话
I'll tell Milena about Jorge.
我会告诉米莱娜豪尔赫的遭遇
Their wounds match Franzy's.
他们的伤口跟弗朗茨的吻合
Meaning he was tortured and tossed out of a helicopter.
这意味着他受到了折磨 然后被扔下了直升机
Uh, one other thing.
还有一件事
Um, no one using any of the names you gave me have checked into any of the hotels in town.
没有人用你给我的名字 登记入住任何酒店
And I talked to my counterparts at the other casinos.
我跟其他赌场的同行谈过了
Orozco and Sanchez, they weren't working on anything for any of them.
奥罗斯科和桑切斯 没有替他们查任何案子
And when I told them about the $65 million gambling scam,
我跟他们说六千五百万的赌博骗局时
they pulled their overnight audits. I did, too.
他们连夜查账 我也是
Everything is within acceptable loss margins.
一切都在可接受的损失幅度中
No one has hit any of the casinos.
没有人以任何一家赌场为目标
You don't have anything to worry about.
你不必担心
Bodies were found in New York, car that followed us was from New York.
尸体都是在纽约发现的 跟踪我们的车是从纽约来的
New York ghost tags, New York parking pass.
是纽约的幽灵车牌和停车证件
This has always been a New York case.
这一直是纽约的案子
Where the hell are you going?
你要去哪里
We're gonna need more guns.
我们需要更多的枪